  //Define questions (Object)
  var questionSource = [
    {
        question: "Questions 1 : Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
        choices: ["a. <javascript>", "b. <script>", "c. <js>", "d. <scripting>"],
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 2 : How to write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
        choices: ["a. if i=5", "b. if (i==5)", "c. if i=5 then", "d. if i==5 then"],
        answer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 3 : How do you create a function in JavaScript",
        choices: ["a. function = myFunction()", "b. function myFunction()", "c. function:myFunction()", "d. createMyFunction()"],
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 4 : How do you call a function named myFunction?",
        choices: ["a. call myFunction()", "b. call function myFunction()", "c. myFunction()", "d. call myFunction"],
        answer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 5 : To see if two variables are equal in an if / else statement you would use ____.",
        choices: ["a. =", "b. ==", "c. 'equals'", "d. !="],
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 6 : The first index of an array is ____.",
        choices: ["a. 0", "b. 1", "c. 8", "d. any"],
        answer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 7 : How does a WHILE loop start?",
        choices: ["a. while i = 1 to 10", "b. while (i<=10)", "c. while(i<=10;i++)", "d. while{i=6}"],
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 8 : Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML elementHow does a FOR loop start?",
        choices: ["a. for (i=0;i<=5)", "b. for(i=0;i<=5;i++)", "c. for i = 1 to 5", "d. for (i<=5;i++)"],
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 9 : How do you round the number 7.25, to the nearest integer?",
        choices: ["a. rnd(7.25)", "b. Math.round(7.25)", "c. Math.rnd(7.25)", "d. round(7.25)"],
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Questions 10 : How do you find the number with the highest value of x and y?",
        choices: ["a. ceil(x,y)", "b. Math.ceil(x,y)", "c. top(x,y)", "d. Math.max(x,y)"],
        answer: "d"
    }
  ];